{
    "subject": "resource/Twitter",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Internet",
    "human_readable": "Twitter's industry is the Internet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6674177050590515,
            "question": "What industry does Twitter operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5624807476997375,
            "question": "What sector is Twitter a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46492987871170044,
            "question": "In what area of online services does Twitter function?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45219284296035767,
            "question": "What kind of network is Twitter a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4497811496257782,
            "question": "Which online space does Twitter belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4182198941707611,
            "question": "Is Twitter primarily involved in the technology or finance industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33142417669296265,
            "question": "What type of platform is Twitter considered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22562503814697266,
            "question": "What realm of digital interaction does Twitter exist within?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20263643562793732,
            "question": "To what broader category of businesses does Twitter belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15831053256988525,
            "question": "What digital sphere is Twitter most associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Twitter's industry is the Internet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3168_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what broader category of businesses does Twitter belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3168_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What realm of digital interaction does Twitter exist within?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3168_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of platform is Twitter considered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3168_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_178.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3168_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"Twitter's industry is the Internet.\" While not explicitly stated, details such as its rapid growth, public usage, and business applications all indicate it operates within the internet ecosystem."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}